<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Academic</title>
    <link>https://phosseini.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://phosseini.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://phosseini.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://phosseini.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://phosseini.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://phosseini.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m a PhD student in the Department of Computer Science at the George Washington University (GWU) doing my research under supervision of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.seas.gwu.edu/mona-diab&#34;&gt;Dr. Mona Diab&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.seas.gwu.edu/david-broniatowski&#34;&gt;Dr. David Broniatowski&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My main areas of interest are Artificial intelligence (AI), Machine Learning (ML), and Natural Language Processing (NLP). My current research focuses on providing an analytical framework for understanding how individuals make various decisions on social media, including spread of mis/disinformation and fake news, and more broadly in interconnected networks. I also work on developing NLP models to extract causal relations, explicit or implicit, and counterfactuals in language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before joining GWU, I spent a year at Sharif University of Technology as a visiting researcher focusing on NLP research. Prior to this, my master&amp;rsquo;s thesis, completed at Guilan University, led to development of a sentiment analysis platform for Persian, SentiPers. I am extremely passionate about entrepreneurship, start-ups and innovation. I spent summer of 2017 at Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) as an intern in &lt;a href=&#34;http://entrepreneurship.mit.edu/accelerator/&#34;&gt;Delta v&lt;/a&gt; program, leading development of the NLP platform of a FinTech startup (Sigma Ratings).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside work, I play beach/indoor volleyball (current member of the GWU Men Volleyball Club, team A) and ping pong (member of the GWU Ping Pong club, team A, 2018) whenever I get a chance. I’ve been also playing &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tonbak&#34;&gt;Tonbak&lt;/a&gt; for more than 17 years.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
