<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | </title>
    <link>https://phosseini.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://phosseini.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://phosseini.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://phosseini.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://phosseini.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://phosseini.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Pedram is a PhD student in the department of Computer Science at the George Washington University (GWU) doing his research under supervision of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.seas.gwu.edu/mona-diab&#34;&gt;Dr. Mona Diab&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.seas.gwu.edu/david-broniatowski&#34;&gt;Dr. David Broniatowski&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His main areas of interest are Artificial intelligence (AI), Machine Learning (ML), and Natural Language Processing (NLP). Pedram’s current research focuses on providing an analytical framework for understanding how individuals make various decisions on social media, including spread of mis/disinformation and fake news, and more broadly in interconnected networks. He also works on developing NLP models to extract causal relations, explicit nd implicit, in language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before joining GWU, Pedram spent a year at Sharif University of Technology as a visiting researcher focusing on NLP research. Prior to this, his master&amp;rsquo;s thesis, completed at Guilan University, led to development of a sentiment analysis platform for Persian. Pedram is extremely passionate about entrepreneurship, start-ups and innovation. He spent summer of 2017 at Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) as an intern in Delta v program, leading development of the NLP platform of a FinTech startup (Sigma Ratings). Outside work, Pedram plays beach/indoor volleyball and ping pong (member of team A at GWU,) whenever he gets a chance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
